Who is this asshole, exiled one?
I need to know who this person is.
I'll just leave it at that.
You just let me know.
I don't know what this person's problem is.
What, I don't know.
I don't remember ever doing anything to this person.
decided to just have them on my panel and stuff big mistakes just like letting any
Chewch opposite Street join my panel, but
you know
And Chewch is the right word for this person
Yeah, I just need to know a little bit of information please contact me anyhow
Hopefully, we're having a good day. What is the day? It's the 19th? October 19th?
Ooh, the 19th. N1019. Okay. Got 911 in there.
So maybe this is an emergency day or something.
Oh, I don't know if, oh, shit, I need to get somebody,
message to somebody.
You just missed the intro, it's okay, Sam, man.
Here, listen to this song.
I like this one.
You got it, you got a ghost.
Crystal Marie, on a midnight stream, neon eyes and conspiracy dreams, talking calls in the desert sands, tattoo maps and shaking hands. She's got screenshots, names and dates.
A tinfoil halo, ceiling fades in a chatroom chapel
Saints confess every broadcast feels like a holy mass
She's cookie, she's hot, she might be right
Dropping bombs in the middle of the night
White rose, black vans, symbol sex
Oh Lord, what will she say next?
Where are you going?
I'm not here.
She's part oracle, part in a net myth, half the room's scared
The rest subsist, her eyeliner sharp as a truth dissected
And every theory leaves the chat infected
You can laugh, but you're still tuned in
Because she's chaos wrapped in porcelain skin
Hey, ghost
Yeah, I have a question. Yes, sir
Why is that song so much cooler than my song because I'm just getting better and better at making them and so
Yes, I'll make you a new go song
You earned one
I have to think of like some inside jokes
Was actually very beautiful
But yeah, I love it. I love almost all my almost all my songs. I just love you know, it's like
And I'm not like
At this point we've heard it so many times I need a better song. Okay. Yes, I'll make it today
And yeah, I mean
Let me point out this the only reason I said that is because you have those glasses on
Oh, thank you. Like these glasses. Yeah, you look at Matt Murdoch. You look like a daredevil, sir
Well, thank you
Thank you
Right there. I'll tell you that
And I got just a look and I got Rudy here here. Look at Rudy
Hey, don't bring that fat ass in the camera. All right, Rudy. Well the cats brought in a big rat last night
and that was like kind of like
I call it
When I can't bring you a mouse a dead mouse, you know, it's like a sign of love
Yes, and then they low-lo started kissing me and then guess what guess who came last night pie
I don't know if you remember pie my kid might
They like you. I know what you said by kiss, but they like you though. Oh my god. She was she was
Like you're fucking licking me. It's like
But if you remember I had a cat named pie and
Last night I heard one for trick tricks was making a growl
He makes his growl only when there was an intruder in the house and I was like what is a raccoon or something inside?
I was like looking in the kitchen
No
It was growling that sound means that there's something in the house isn't like
And Lola brought in a rat and stuff, so I was like,
maybe there's a rat, but then I looked
and there's like a black cat.
And I was like, oh, there's Lenore.
And then I was like.
She gave me her attention though.
She loves you, that's why she brought it to you.
She does but but but so I heard tricks and then um, I thought it was Lenore
Like the black cat and I looked in Lenore sitting over here
Dogs I never asked you this question
My family are huge dog lovers cat
Do you do you know why a dog looks at you and it poops?
Because it's like looking at you for like safety or something. Yeah, it's powerful like like hey protect me make they feel vulnerable
Yeah
I
Wouldn't wonder I literally just like figured that out. I
Always wanted that all my life like what is why are you looking at my eye when you pooping?
Because they they at least you're gonna protect them if not you're gonna say something and like hey somebody behind you
Like that's what they think. I'll put your song on Jamie
No, no, no, no fuck Jamie. I want go song ghost sober. Let's run one
So
Jamie you can have the second one
Where's my song oh
Jamie come boys
I'm sorry. Okay. Yeah, Jamie. I will play your song too. Um, I want my song please and I want a new fucking song
Okay, yeah
Play it now
Which one Jamie yeah, play Jamie she asked for
I don't have a video for Jamie's yeah, I need to
See I can get her her song on
But yeah, I just want to tell you in case you guys remember my cat pie. It was like a black cat. That was like
I had like I want to give a shout out to fish tacos. They're very great. I love them
I'm gonna give a shout out to the pier
I'm gonna give a shout out to Mikey
He might be a dumb dumb, but he's my friend. Oh
Well, thank you ghost
That's the closest thing you're ever gonna get saying like I love you. I like you now
He might be a dumb dumb, but he's my friend. That's the closest thing you're ever gonna get that's
Coming from you that is a huge compliment. I love it. Thank you. Thank you
So let me get to Jamie song. I actually have two versions of it
I haven't played one of the versions for so maybe I'll get the other version. I don't play it. Let me see
Um, Jamie, where is it? Oh, Jamie Cowboy song. Here it is. Okay. Let me see the song.
Thank you, Ghost. I won't forget you.
Oh, yeah. So this is the new one. Okay. So Jamie, here's the other version for you. Okay.
This is Jamie's Cowboy song. Enjoy.
Why did Jamie get a song?
Jamie she's my top mod. She's been my mod since I started the show she's been my mods
Like she's been like she's always here always like hey, when are you going on?
I mean, she's like you just you know you too like are like that, but you know she's like
She's been here for a long time and she deserved a song. So here's her here's her
Oh, you know the other version maybe you like this version better Jamie. We'll see
Um, I can we did some right after this if you don't mind. Yes, we can. Yes, we can. But here's the
From the very first string you were holding the line
My bad shine always on time
Greeting every soul that comes through the door you make the chat feel like home
you stand with page and with summer too nobody shakes the faith that runs through you mason
might try but can't break your stride with loyalty and love always by your side jayme
That's why this is your song
You stand with Paige and with Summer too
Nobody shakes the faith that runs through you
Mason might try, but can't break your stride
With loyalty and love, always by your side
Jamie, you're the heart of the room
Lighting up the space like a rising moon
Through the chaos you always stay strong
That's why this is your song
Every reading hits a spark in your soul
Every high you send makes it around the world
There you go, papa.
Let's go, y'all!
Got that ring
and your quickfire mind.
From the late night chaos to the morning light
You've been here holding it down just right
If there's a hall of fame for the real and true
I'd carve your name in Gold Ghost
That's you
I won't forget you
You make me laugh till my face turns blue
You know you do
Your body is hell yeah
It's always a blast
These moments we're making
I'm built to last
Thank you ghost
You're one of a kind
With your big heart I missed you
And you quit
Not Tony, huh? All right, Ghost, I believe you. Maybe.
Whoa! Yeah. Okay, go. Whoa. So, guys, um, yes, that's Ghost's song. I mean, Ghost is gonna
Like I was saying pie the cat
Was inside the house last night and then he like rubbed my leg and oh he left he rubbed my leg and
then he
You know
Tricks was growling at him and he ran out of the house, but he he rubbed against my leg and said hi
And he's fine. He looks big and healthy and big big black cat little strong black cat
Um
Yeah, so ghosts or yeah, so you know he's back
Hopefully he'll come in again, but you know tricks is kind of
Yeah, there we go. Yeah, I remember pie
No, I actually pie was like hardly even here when I started the show
I think he I he'd already kind of burned away. So it's been a while
Wow a year and he's already so he's big he's a big
He looks like a big look. He does look like a panther. I was like, oh my gosh
There's a panther in my house and it was because he's like really like muscular and stuff
He looks and he's all he was big. He just came rubbing on my leg and ran on out, but
It's nice to know like that. He's good. He's safe and he's okay and it looks like he has
I know nothing about that, but you know what it is. It's goes tober. It's goes tober fest. Yep. It is and
Yes
Anyone has information about exiled one contact me, um, please
Just incidentally
Yeah, so okay, so what's up? What's up? What's on the plan for today? You know, I just did find a little
Nug on the floor of we that I smoked. It's pretty good. We're gonna have some fun. I must leave you
We'll have fun you have fun and enjoy the movie. What are you gonna see? Do you know?
Yeah, the neutron of the new tribes thinking that the neutron. Well, I hope it's wonderful and exciting and
You have a fun time enjoy and I'll see you tonight
Thank you ghost you're one of a kind
I won't go get you
Yeah, but um hey Alexander, can you get on the case exiled one you have to figure out who that person is and your information?
I'll get them. You want me to ban? I'll get along
Whoever whoever get some get some actionable get some actionable info on this person
We are I'm taking a page from Alexandra mayors playbook and
Yeah, I'm gonna go Alexandra mayors on his ass, okay
Okay, dope. Thank you. He wants to play with me
By the way, there's there's a scrap metal people like they're probably about
all I'll say there were several people people looking for scrap metal today, but um
The name that they're getting well first of all, they're saying that they talked to my dad my dad who passed away last year
Okay, so that's like not
Well that's what you should be not mention them
And then they say and they say oh it's and are you Alexander Bates?
That's what they asked me. It's a letter X I
LED
We get last night. He was porn bombing. He was
Threatening he said he's got a whole army of undiscord doing Psyops on me. I'll just come bullshit. So yeah
Let me take this time you can exile one and may I talk to him if you don't mind? Yeah, good
You can bring your whole army. You can bring whoever you want. Guess what? You're never gonna fuck me up big ghost is here
I'm down to run one
Okay, thank you
We're gonna do it brother. Oh, yeah, we have we have a we have an army of our own and and he thinks
Me nobody gonna fuck with you when I'm here
Thank you ghost see
God, you know, it's like you when you fuck with me. You're not only fucking with me. You're fucking with the whole psyche
And big ghost absolutely and it's like you know and even supernatural forces are
Involved you know
You guys run one, but guess what you're never gonna do you're never gonna talk shit about big ghost. Oh fuck them up
And if anybody wants to come up here, I'm I'm sure psych will let you up here. He let's everybody up here
Soldiers well
Does somebody want to come in with me, okay come on up
If anyone wants to come around anybody you and all your goonies. That's where I'm
I'll literally do a one versus nine right now. Let's talk in running
Hello, okay. Let's talk in rhyme
Yeah, anyone can come up here. Oh, yeah, put the link
That's a good-looking man right there
Sorry this damn mouse I keep clicking the side
Who who wasn't that did what Samantha taking glasses off I won't say that but those glass that's a good-looking man. Thank you
I picked the right style for me. Oh here. Okay. Someone wants to run it with you. Here we go
Let's run a dog we can run it. How you doing first of all, how you doing to burn a proof is on you
Did you know XI one is Bronzeberg's brother-in-law
Something right now
the
I let me agree with you. I can see that what should like do you think there's like a good point?
We should argue about like what do we disagree about?
Pretty much nothing we always came to terms like you're right ghost you're right Alex like you know we started arguing
But then we realize
I'm being very nice to you because you know ghost sober. I'm being very nice
You know, we can't debate the women up here the crazy ladies
Oh, my who in summer Crystal Marie. Oh my baby. Yep
This summer come eat a white night Christine
Yes
Well, what's crystal is saying that
And it's a Chris that Christine was like, you know trying to like on a live
Streamer named blade by by donating to him like large amounts when he was like, you know
I'm not not like, you know
the
Well, let's not bring him into it. I'm just kidding. We can't we can't we can't we can't I mean it's like that's fine
For just what talking
I can't really make a ghost out. I don't know if he's muffled a little. I mean it sounds loud, but
Alex the crystal was saying like I do I am aware of like people like the look at people as
Lowel cows and and do donate
Generously to them, but basically it's just to fuck them up like I mean it's but I'm not saying that she's involved or anything like that at all
Wait, hold on. You're losing me now too. Who's a low count? Who's donating to who hold on?
Many Blanco like he had these mods that did a secret discord group and I'm like the messages were leaked and I read the messages and
They're saying oh, let's let's I'm gonna donate a hundred dollars to him. So he buys, you know a bottle of
Jack and he drinks the bottle and oh wow donating to hurt you like I'm gonna donate so he does this and fucks his whole shit up on live
Yeah, I think okay
So that concept is familiar to me like just because and then it's like also the same thing happened to um
base and I mean not based or for world t-shirts Josh walk and then also to
I can see that that's crazy. That's trolling at its finest. That's like real sick shit
But you're not saying ghost is doing that to you, right?
No, I'm saying that was um, but the crystal is they making the allegation that Christine was doing it
Christine was doing it to a
The guy in blade. I don't know
I don't know man. Honestly. I don't know Christine that well. She's that evil. I know on these panels if she has passed
History on these panels and did that I don't know like that's just too much
I'm gonna bring the process
I just know a chicken lady, you know
You as much as you know, it's like that's what I know
you know I know and I don't think she would from what I know like you know like that doesn't
right yeah we know it's a crazy allegation but you know what summer came up and it was like hey
christmas i'm outside your window it's like this thing it's some funny shit and like uh she's
trolling her yeah and then we found out who there's somebody named summer's mouth or something some
summer's mouth and it's like who's on the panel yeah the trolls have been going crazy lately
this is the
summer's mouth is chrysalmary
and she came up
yeah
that's that's mental
Yeah, I mean they were
They both have photos of like, you know, some like mouth
I don't know whose mouth or what it was from like a Google website or something. I don't know
It's a yeah, it's kind of a pain game. It's like a that's awesome, man. Thank you
Yeah, I've been having fun the past week on your panels the pastor all the shit you private it or put on memberships only
all those panels
They were fine. They were fine. Yeah, exactly, Bill. And I'm gonna, you know, I'm gonna as I can, you know
Make them available to everyone, but yeah, I am a member but on my other
I'm a member on an account that I deleted so it's still
I'm still a member. I'm still going to get charged at the end of the month
But I can no longer like type as a member because I deleted that account and started a new one
Like so I'm not a member on this one. That's why when you see your members, you'll see me like member
Yeah, but but I can't do the little emojis anymore
I'm a little star
And I can't view the fucking membership shit. Yeah, I wanted to see me and Janet fighting
That was fun. Play that again, maybe. Okay, so I think we have Justine coming up. Do you know Justine? I don't know and put the banner up, Dick. Thank you. This is me. Hey, how are you? Hey, I'm good. I'm just gonna come on and hey, I don't know who you are, but Mr. Hey, whoever you are, if it's not being rude, I just don't know your name and I can't say it.
Okay, okay psyche really quick. Yes. Am I are you and me okay?
Yeah, I mean I remember was like you were like unmod me or like you know, you know, you know
I was modded and then I got unmodded and that hurt my feelings, which would naturally be
And then I I have been blocked
So I'm just wondering if I wanted everybody, but I'll look into my list and I'll rebodge you too
I mean, it's like I have been blocked too. So I'm just making sure that me and you are okay because you know what I
Care about you because I think we are we have the we are we are kindred souls
I think are you from Australia?
No, I'm Canadian
She's not familiar
This is grace for this is grace for
Your grace for man, oh god, I'm good
Continue
I'm from Abbotsford, BC, which is
Do you know a girl named Paige? She's like the Princess of Canada prairie wind
No, I don't know who Paige is but I would like to meet her
She's so Canadian would I would like to meet thing that is as Canadian and
And Canada dry and her dry and it's girlfriend that he hides behind his back every
Yeah, I just wanted to come up here, and I don't want to crowd you out. I'm gonna go
Bro, I just heard the beat in her
I've met her
I'd like to just seen on camera. She did like a she was like saying a song and she's in the CFF. She's got his friend
Yeah, I really like gaudy and gaudy likes me and we're all good friends and I just want to know that I really like you
psyche
What am I job-living coming up here because what I do if I feel that people I just want to come up and ask you
So that I don't make assumptions
Yeah, yeah, that's a good idea because
One day one day Alex
the
Do come on man
Other people were warning you wasn't just me the chat was warning you to people that hated me said it like Alex
I hate your guts, but she's worse like I agree with Alex on this and you wouldn't heed
But it's okay. She hasn't left my lovely avocado, and she's
Avocado she she got me with the same little boy
Little boys
I'm smoking 97% end of God vape
nice
I'm not I don't I I'm a real smoker from 93
93 oh
No one has ever died of we right
Cigarettes go people every day. I don't think there's one case of someone dying from weed
Yeah, they what they what happens is is that weed is sometimes spliced with stuff
Yeah, yeah
That's when it gets laced that it gets fucked up and then if you get cancer from that because there's
In the way you smoke it if you're smoking that shit in duchess and like these filly that brown garbage paper that's cancerous too
Yeah, I know
In a bang or a vaporizer
Yeah, you have to be careful
You have to be careful and they and you have to be careful where you buy it because I heard that there is
They spray they spray to a smells
Yeah, like this is strawberry fucking indigo and they just spray with some strawberry shit. Yeah
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
the
No, that's great.
Yeah, there is.
You don't expect them to eat cocaine.
They stick it in everything.
Yeah, okay.
I got you, man. That's crazy.
But then you got to trust your healer.
You're a trustee dealer. You buy weed from the guy your life. You can't make me look better
Just see I didn't see on the block list just seen so I think you can type in chat. Okay. Oh my god. Did you see what just happened that?
I'm gonna skedaddle. Oh my god
My name is hanging out with you
In you to name less boy friend my boyfriend mr. Name. Let's
Thank you. That's the best name I've ever heard mr. Nameless. Oh fuck psych on LES is um
He had a road mod man and
He blocked his whole his whole inventory and everyone's up there one the easy Apollo
And they got tortured for about an hour street. So they were timing out everyone in the chat
They said it was me. Everyone was easy wonder. It's Alex. It's Alex and they couldn't figure out how to stop it
Bro for an hour the funniest thing I've ever seen so someone like Katrina would bring them back after they got blocked
But they just kept happening and happening and they would ban the person and it just kept happening and happening and for an hour
And they were going crazy
Oh my god, what's happening? We've never seen nothing like this people coming up like yo
I've never seen nothing like this like what the fuck like it's Alex
It's Alex. It was the funniest thing to the point that he had to take the panel down
No, no, okay
No, no, okay. I wish I had the technology to just keep blocking at anyone's Jesus
So they were like he gave a wrench to the wrong person and they went crazy tonight
And they couldn't figure out who it was and they were guiding him how to go to the into the studio
And it was the funniest thing but it was like an hour for them to figure it out
And he was like, okay, I found the blacklist and they were like look for like
Moderators and then it was fucking funny in the meantime the whole plan is getting blocked block block block
Let's say it was funny actually they were laughing Wanda was loving it. She was like, oh my god
You just got blockchain rock like you only did it again ha ha Wanda so funny. You know, I know what the fuck
They just keep doing it. They just keep doing it
He blocked me at that poem bomb them
Well, you know Alex that is like, you know, no, no, but well, I broke his cherry and he'd need I bet you I saved his life
Well, yeah, nice and early in the game. So now he'll never get pulled on again
I don't want him to go through what you've been through bro getting pulled on 30 times a day
Because this channel like I mean you just start or no
He just started like a month ago, bro. Exactly. So I traumatized him off the bat and now he's on high alert
Nobody goes up without the banner. You understand like I did a good thing like he might never get poor mom again
Like my one little poor mommy is gonna save him a lifetime
If you are nice to me
I can tell them like impelable information about all kinds of things and it's like and it's like and I would
And I shared this information about because I learned a lot of stuff on like like going through YouTube and there's thousands of hours
I'm doing shows and blah blah. Yeah, and I still you know, I still you know, we'll get like, you know
People porn bombing occasionally and stuff like that. But I just put you put your guard down
That's all but you already know how to stop it like it happened last night again, right?
The guy with the fucking shit on the cock and then it happened another guy came up shirtless and you just you know
No screening at all. You're like, oh look, it's a hot dude with no shirt and boom cock
Like you have to screen them all but when you're that fucked up and having a good time
I get it like just forget and you know, it's like oh new person. Look, it's a hot dude cock
But I mean there are ways around a lot of stuff like you know
The ways are you have to get it through your head that anytime someone's trying to come up
You have to put the banner up and identify them make them talk
Even if it's a DJ let's show because don't put a picture, you know, you got a hero
I keep taking not really as powerful as they think they are though
And it's like, you know, and it's like, yes, if you've just been, oh, no, it's not powerful.
That's actually the point is the banner.
And then he said, like, to the F word, F-A-G-G-O-T.
And then I was like, OK, well, I don't know the person.
It was it was a woman's woman's profile name and picture or whatever.
And that it was man talking.
And then and then he just when he did it again, he's like, oh, you're a dumb F-A-G-G-O-T.
And it wasn't it wasn't trying to word bomb you.
just in case they can't poem bomb you, they're going to do anything to at least word bomb you
so they can report any type of hateful content.
That's so crazy though. Yeah
Yeah, so but you know you learned the lesson last night because you never got bomb-bomb by a live person
It's always like an avatar and they switch it
Person was a video. They're playing exactly correct, but it was still a live person, which I told money for 20 ones
They can do that. Exactly. They don't put a video. They can even do that of beta. That's the scary part
And you'll believe it's me. They're like, Hey, like, or
Emperor Janet, like they'll clip a video of her. And then she'll
be in the back and you'll be like, Oh, it's Empress, you let her
up. And it's a video for like, Hey, psych, they'll clip it from
whatever episode to make it look like, you know, she's saying
high psych and cock. It's fucking crazy. So at that point of
the game, you have to screen them enough to be 100% that it's
them and not a video.
Yeah, it's a self
Okay, thank you very much. I think that is man. Jesus. I still got a project sort of man
I was just trolling the guy, you know me. I like to troll. Oh, I didn't know man
Mom's give me a favor. Mom's make sure you're on all messages
Make sure it's because it's been defaulting to top messages
Make sure you click the little wheel on top and say all messages. You can see some of the
Things that are being said that maybe you're missing because I see all the comments coming up here
I forget to turn it on to you
But I see them comments on stream yard all the comments and so all messages and top messages are different
Yeah, top messages are like so they they screen out some of the
If it sometimes they can if it's like okay, so you can say top messages like I don't want to see every single bullshit
Spam thing just the top messages. I got a message. It is where I want to see everything
I need the mods to see all the messages. Yeah, correct on your percent
And I'm putting the link up right now
because that person someone was just saying oh you know HIV awakens tarot and stuff and Jesus see
that needs to be blocked immediately blocked banned time down and things and it was in the top messages
and so you all people would have seen it so you miss it some people see it and some don't you know
there be friendly otherwise they're saying oh hi alexander mcqueen and stuff like that but then
it's like um then that was the second thing they said it's like oh hi HIV awakens tarot and so I
just want to do things like that you can just click them off anything wants to come up for a minute
But see how fake jackets work man, even with that LES shit the last panel they swore was me for an hour
There was multiple people saying it's Alex of talix. Oh my god. It's Alex. He's doing he's blocking everybody
They even brought you up like psyche gave me a wrench and he erased everybody like it's our house Alex
And I'm sitting back like it's not me your fucking retards
You know saying
Jesus
Like hi Alex little thing
Hey, man listen, what really pissed me off about the other day Alex was the next morning
My mother needed needed to have the ambulance called. Oh God. She fainted in the garden
Of course, that really pissed me off because you were trying to make me feel bad
For taking care of my mother and the next morning. She really needed it. Jesus. I was fucking fuming the next day
But I'm okay. Wow. That's God smacking me in the face or both. Oh, I don't know what the hell that is
That's crazy. What are the coincidences? Yeah? Well, I mean
And then the next day she runs off and does like that whole live about it. I was like
I think that's a wonderful thing. They're taking care of you know your family and things like that
Yeah, man. That's just YouTube, right? They're gonna take anything and troll the shit out of you
I know that's why I didn't want to divulge it right away, but it's just circumstance, right? It's just the way things worked out
In my life
I was the only one I was the only one that was available that could do it and some
that's
And now you tell me your mom being an ambulance in the morning, so
Yeah, very next morning. That was something
Yeah, you know what I see my friends treat their parents like shit sometimes curse at them like they go crazy and
I'm just like breaks my heart
Like when they're gone, you're gonna miss their craziness. You're gonna miss them. I know you're gonna miss them call you like
Like we don't see that
Like fuck stop calling me so much like i got it mom like what up with that like fuck but when they're gone, man
You're gonna be like fuck like they're both at that age
Of course, of course you're going on with me right now. I know you're pretty annoying time
But they're at that age now right like i'm almost 60 years old i'm 58 so they're in their late 70s 80s
Yeah, oh, I mean they're at that point where you got to worship every second of them because you don't know now
You know it sucks that we
the
That's all it is Alex I was really pissed about the next day so that's all it's not a big deal. I'm not I'm not embarrassed
To be in the situation, but it can't be embarrassing because someone can make it embarrassing
You know, yeah, I don't like when my children go sideways. This has happened a couple times
You're not the first like two or three times big shit like I told people and like it went into like real life
Somehow and then why do you do that?
Are you bipolar or something like why do you just probably I don't know I know that that knows but
Okay, anyways, I just wanted to come up and say that I'd clear the air like I'm not pissed at you guys
I was just playing
No, no, I got stuff to do anyways, I'm just listening
Okay guys talk to you later, maybe
Or guys
Oh shit, oh yeah, that's why that did that one. Okay, got that. Yeah, there's ghost that's what it's ghost over I
Need to check out. I think something I need I can speak something real quick. Oh, it's like I just need to check something out real quick
In my students
Okay
Okay, oh
Are you still there? Okay live
I'm here. I thought you need to check some out. So I'm muted up. Okay
OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK
it's not boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy boy
Because this will be key, okay
Custom got the link I gotta run through the little ladies room give me a second
Okay
Okay one second
Two
Okay
Okay, I think I got really lucky guys. Okay, where is it?
Okay, I can do that
one
says driving me nuts, oh my god
hold on, shit
did I hear nuts?
like hairy nuts?
you heard hairy nuts
let's do the AI thing bro
let's run it, the AI cop
UIS AI two questions last night and a fucking compliment to me both times before it answered me
Does that happen to you? Does the thing say?
Yeah
I was tripping. I'm like, oh
the
that's how good it is, like, it can...
Yeah, yeah.
That's scary, bro.
Doing that, and then, you know, there's a little bit of a...
We all need to take every penny we have and invest in AI right now,
because that should...
What at the cost of exploding?
Do you understand that, humans?
It's just being invented.
That's just going to blow up in the next 10 years.
invest in the A.I., ASAP, and Tesla, and Google all those shits, just invest, baby.
But, you know, it's going to blow up in the next 10 years.
Shit.
Oh, okay. I need to fix this shit.
What are you looking for?
Oh, there I ask.
I think I got it. I think I got it.
Oh, hold on.
I can't believe Crystal Marie in summer went at it.
Um, I'm gonna call it a draw right now a draw a good smart man smart man
Yeah, I don't I hope I hope that they can you know, maybe work it out, but um, I
Don't they don't know I just don't know
Let's see what's going on here
Okay, I ain't got it. Okay. Got it. I think I got it. Can I save you shit?
This is gonna drive me nuts, okay
I woke up this morning and I was still in the studio, bro
You were I don't know when you ended it or what but I just think I fell asleep
I woke up and I said you're in the studio is just me
Said you're in the show like what show
Okay, Janet and Chris is the funniest on earth
Natalie Queen Natalie
Yeah
Queen Natalie she's awesome too awesome
Okay
Freakin figure this out. We see can I do this?
Okay, and I can go oh shit and I can go like this
Okay, and then a ghost wants to run one he says in the back chat
Wait, how could be in the back chat if he's not in the show
He's in the back chat, okay
Supposedly but don't you have to be up here to be in the back job?
Okay, okay. Yeah, I get he's in the back stage. There he is
Little ghosty pool
You make me crazy because I hear people's voices that sound like people up here in real life
And I'm like the fuck is that ghost like the other day that guy um was a GT
One of those guys Ziggy. I was somewhere, bro
And someone was talking like behind me and it sounded exactly like like I thought I was on the panel
I turn around like what the fuck
Are you there?
ghosty ghosty
Ghosty Ronys
Hey, you miss a song or something that says I'm not Tony. He's holding up a car saying I'm I'm not Tony
You're funny
Totally not Tony is random guy Tony bro because you guys are fucking with me
I don't I don't know I can't I don't I don't get it though
So are you guys friends like I don't get it? You know Tony's Tony, you know random guys Tony
But yeah, he's on your panel and he's sending me new or oh by the way
I want to ask you has that come down a little or is it still the thing down every day
People came to the door today saying oh, my name is Alexander Bates
what and
Alexander Bates and I said my father
Father on the phone and stuff like that and totally right. Oh, they're going hardcore. So you think it's XI one I
Shit is
He was like the porn bomber last night was not was not a
Tony it was a you know, XL one so XL one
Yeah, so he told me he's though. He's been trolling for 20 years 20 psych
I've been on YouTube for two years. This guy said he's been trolling for 20 years. He says he's the king troll
He says he's been trained by the best some guy veto. I don't know who the fuck 20 years ago
So XI one doing them
Purpose like total sense. Oh, he's just a retard. I mean, he's like really stupid
I mean, he's like, oh go to discord and like, you know flop behind the scenes or whatever
But he already he's married to bronze bird sister
Not his biological sister. By the way, it's an adopted sister. So this little family are like a bunch of Greeks
I talked to that woman before and she was yeah fucking. What's her name? Um?
But she's a nice lady. She got no, she's beautiful. She's she cams up. She's hot. She's beautiful the fact she's married to
Exile one is disgusting though
I don't think that's gonna last soon that girl's gonna wake up one day and be like look at this guy married to some loser
Fucking troll for 20 years. He's here fucking
bombings I click that's not a man
Eventually get sick of like bullshit and little boy
Jewish dad whatever he is he is like this he was like trolling in his private time and like you know
It looks his wife's like why is he spending all the time away from me? You know, it was just it was just because
classic
so I'm going to do something and put this on
Joe point two point oh, Joe
I think that guy's from TPP
I mean new TPP
There's like a new and old, you know, like new money old money like I'm old money TVP, but there's some like new
OK. Oh, this one's ready too. Yeah. This is good. This is good.
Yo, fucking Arthur.
Ha ha. Who the fuck is that Arthur, dude? He's so funny.
I caught a panel dealer. They were easy, came up for two seconds,
and then Arthur right behind them.
Like, yo, you're a scumbag, aren't you?
Like, I saw you. I saw you. You stab, motherfucker. I can't wait.
I was like, yo, Arthur is bugging.
And then he ran off. Like, this is why I don't come on your panel.
So like, wee wee wee. He just left.
My man Arthur
And Sam and shoo another maniac
Yeah, he's a mad man same man Air Force Sammy
to
I didn't feel very lucky. I feel very blessed. Yeah
Portionate and it's true J dog says there's a lot of people that do care about you still like, you know
You think like everyone's against you and that's not true. You have a good team on your side
Yeah, I do your J dog. Was that a gay bar yesterday?
Did you hear they were trolling him and calling the bar and tell him like to kick him out?
Now who does that? Is that is that Tony Bologna? Who's the madman?
behind these antics
Who watches J-Dog are alive calls the bar he's at somehow knows what bar he's at
Dox is him like a mr. Bartender like you see that guy like and they actually kicked him out of like three bars. I
Mean I find that also like that is a little harassing whatever man, but that's fucking comedy at his finest, baby
if you're gonna troll if you're gonna do something do it good you understand
Don't do it Fs. I
Can't believe they send Alexander base to your house
Was it
the
Did they call him and then he directs him to my place so it's impossible to find out where it's coming from
I mean, I could probably just google the number while the phone number on craze. I could I could yeah
Well, you just keep that cool of yours psyche, you understand that's your meal ticket that cool of yours
They want you to come out of your face one day all drunk and fucked up like fuck yeah
Stop coming to mass grandma and stop punching people and shit, you know, they're probably taping that shit
Just keep that cool yours
Like no wrong wrong door
Yep
Okay, well, I feel really good right now because I was able to do something very important. And so, okay, um, yeah
I do I am cool calm collected. I'm gonna keep going. I'm gonna like, you know taking doesn't go
I'm working really hard. Um
I'm really proud of what I've done. I'm actually jealous bro. They love you dick. I don't get fucking scrap metal people on my door
of the
just laughing like
Grab my little my boys
I'm important to for them to worry about but you know
I'm still on top and it's like wow. Wow. Are they are they upset? You know that I'm getting you know
You know who you got a
They said they did this to groovy G me G me. Oh
My god, the Spanish just came out of me G me
that was your target
They used to do is to go be Jimmy now you're the new Jimmy
That was a spanish think about it now who did that to him? It's the same people doing it to you
like our team Tony Bologna and
God knows who else
So I do have permission. Can I fuck him up? Okay?
Go ahead
No, no
Look at you asking psych permission cuz you know who's panel is this big dog
Exactly did you see a bomb on them and almost all your donations went away, but he was able to edit it
It was an accident ghost
I was trying to show fucking this girl's fucking dirty feet. It would have been hilarious
You would say feet me with the girls don't cause you're did no page page
She was golfing and then she took their little slippers off when she didn't know
Let me run one Alex you want to run one let's run one. Let's run it. Let's run it. Thank you. Let us run it
Okay
Go ahead Alex. You can start
Right back
You're the one that wants to run it you want to make the score 120 to 2
Because we're at 119 to 2 right now. So you want me to get another one?
There the actual answer is 43 to 2 I won 43 times
No, that's on a good you're thinking of a speakeasy's
Super store
You don't know you don't know what you're talking about
Let us have a conversation if you don't let's run it dick. Let's run it pick a top
You don't know the fuck it. Oh, here's my top. You don't fuck you're talking about about anything
You don't wanna diaper do you I'd like to run it if you don't
Know who it's shepherd
It's goes tober. Shut the fuck up and run it go ahead
A door shepherd in the middle shepherd in the middle
Fuck up boy. Yeah
See I like shepherd's hair. I'm gonna go with that look because I gotta comb it forward. I keep
See he's a good looking dude. He's got the cheeks that the nose is perfect
Huh, what are you singing Lion King?
You know what I like bro, I like um Annie the son will come out tomorrow tomorrow
Bet your bottom dollar
That the Sun will come out
It can't rain every day goes remember that can rain every day
can be rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain rain
the
Well, you know
Like in the beginning of his song is just that they should say like I paid a lot of money for this
You got to make it shorter that's like I paid a lot of money for this
Look ghost always wins five dollars what a cheapo
He was dropping fifty hundred now. He's back to five. You know, he broke his little piggy bank
This guy probably has two hundred hours a week for me to hear something drops on you're trying to look hard
And now he's back to little five hours
Arbiter or biter. Actually, it's not a orbiter. It's our biter
Interesting I
Like that orange fucking Jason in my man
My background guy I like the background
What are you doing shepherd, where are you what in the hemisphere are you Canadian too?
No, no, I live I live in the same city as a
Psyche but I live on the other side of California
Yeah, we don't do another side of redondo like you're redondo man, too. Oh, wow
If you look up Trader Joe's in redondo, that's like I'm around the corner from there. What's the best?
Getting cold here man. We're down though. It's just always beautiful right over here. Oh
I'm not really good with cool. I'm not good with hot weather like I sweat when I go outside and
Yeah
It's unbearable sometimes like it's
Walk too fast like when I like when I go like to when I go to like trade or doze and come back home
I think I I think I walk really fast or something. That's that's probably what it is
You gotta pace yourself now. You can just order to the house. You don't have to leave
Amazon fucking they call it Amazon pressure some shit. I
Don't I don't do that. I just use cash for everything. I'm like, I'm like one of those
cashman
Me too
Cassius King
Until it's not right until they raise it but so far cash is king
Everyone just wants to see that blue hundred dollar bill
The blues
when you go like when you go to like different countries and you like like if you go to London or something you see their money like
It's like really strange. But then when you get back here, it's like, oh, I remember this shit
It's like
You know other countries have like a mural on their fucking dollar bills, right?
It's like a president's face the whole history of the country's
Their money is like
It's like what am I doing here?
And it means and it's worthless right it says like a million a million on it and you could buy something
It's like a dollar look what the fuck you know, and it's just called it a dollar
What the worst country in the world is?
It's is beat as country here. I ran
Dollar over there. It's like 150 of their money. It's 150 of their money
How much?
One dollars one hundred feet. No, no, no, Colombia. You ready for this one pal?
One American dollar in Colombia is five thousand pesos
Yeah, so two dollars is ten thousand pesos and then you know a hundred dollars forget it a thousand dollars
You're like a billy there out there
But I paid three grand a month in rent. I can pay in Columbia
My cousin has an apartment. She pays one month of my rent
Three grand pays her whole rent for a year in Colombia
And she lives in a beautiful building with a poor doorman the whole shit
Three grand in the United States can pay your whole rent for a year in a luxury apartment in Colombia a year 12 months
It was I was born there. Oh, you were yeah, that's a while back. What are you like 45 like me? I'm around there
Yep, I'm right there right there
Yeah, baby
Yeah, a lot of countries are like that. You can like I don't know. There's like a ton of countries
I was talking to my cousin. I swear to God. She's like, what do you pay? She's I was like this
She's like in US dollars. I'm like, yeah monthly like for the past 10 years. She's like, oh my god
I'm like, what are you paying? She tells me in pesos what it is like 2 million pesos. I don't know what it is
I'm like, oh my god, I can pay your rent for a year with one of one month of my rent
We'll pay your whole rent for a year. That's insane
Exactly, so yeah, I can stop paying rent here monthly go to Columbia get a luxury apartment
Pay it for the whole year with one month here worth and then have 11 months of just free income to
fuck away
Yeah, and then like and the girls feel that shit. They're like you could you'd be like you banging girls like left and right
You can't go to those countries. They did they just go all over you like oh save me
$100 there is more money than I see in a month, bro
You know I'm saying people work there a month for $200 a month. I
Waste $200 before I walk out of my house, bro
Just fucking gas food and fucking tolls is $200 for a day
That's what they make there in a month
Yeah
That's scary
And you know funny thing is when she showed me her palm, and I'm like fuck that's like nicer than my shit
I'm paying three great in the month. I don't got a pole. This bitch has a pole
I'm like what the fuck?
Like we don't have what we hear they got all the channels
Everything yeah, and that's another bill right $100 a month of Netflix. They don't
The poverty that's out there. We have to be appreciated for what we have here in the United States, man
Every time I go to Columbia and come back from vacation. I'm like, oh my god. I'm a king like
People are kids play there with dirt. They don't have toys or us and toys in Amazon
They literally like make steaks and like mud into toys
and we're here like $200 Christmas for like some dumb racetrack that the kid just fucking kicks into the dirt anyway
It's fucking sickening man the inequality on the planet. It's really fucking a fuck for me
They don't have like like the 19th 1980s Nintendo or shit like that. They don't have they do bobo
You got to be rich out there. You'd have to have money like and not everybody. Oh, it's rough
Unless you're selling drugs or like a doctor like
You're gonna live in poverty
That's why I read but that's why the narco trade is so lucrative man. You know people will grow up sucking dirt with
Nothing
They get offered $2,000 more money. They'll ever seen their whole fucking life to do this and people jump all over it little kids
Anything to save my family anything
Everyone's gonna live survive
That's why they can't they'll never stop that
That's why drug trees will never be stopped, bro.
Well, the fucking, the course, you know.
You buy a kilo in Colombia for $2,000 Shepherd check this out. You know what a kilo is a pure cocaine pure
to grand if somehow you have the balls and the connect to get it to Florida
Now it's worth 30 grand if you could get it to New York now. It's worth
$50,000 talk about a profit margin my friend you spent two grand if somehow you can get this stupid little
Brick thing to New York. You're gonna get 48,000 dollars US dollars mother Colombian peso friend
in the stand
Jesus and they're sending megatons for all megatons
I know I threw you up at that who's at the door. Good job psych always put the manner up
Identify talk. Who is it?
the
Oh, yeah, Scottie, it's dogs
It's dogs
You know Canada dry was trolling this shit out of me yesterday
No one likes Canada dry. Fuck him. No, I'm just worried what you're trying to do later, bro
I'm just trying to find out. What's up? How you doing cutie?
Damn
Yeah, I'm just chillin man. I'm just chillin
I like what you know, I like turning on these like crazy shows on cable. It's like
What is it like these ghosts like hunting shows like one is it one of them is like Jack Osborne and the other one is like
Zach Bagan's ghost adventure. I don't know why I'm addicted to those shows like I
Like I got it like stop watch. I'm like I'm addicted to it
You know those shows ghost hunting shows shows
Yeah, I think they're retarded, but I think I think if I'm watching it with you, I bet you it's pretty dope though
Dubs, where do you where do you live? What city are we don't talk about that? Okay?
Well, I'm in Redondo. He's your neighbor, bro. He's a California dondo. Hold on. Shut the fuck up. What's for a dondo?
Redondo, that's where
that
He just like
Yeah, you know he doesn't have the babies hit us, you know, he thinks it's a loan he's modeling it trust me
Yeah, psyche wants that full ball of hair like we like like like fucking
Bowling ball fucking shiny. I'm pretty sure good and shave that head off. She shaved the fucking hair
But that's wax that up. I don't know if I could do it. What it what a to pay maybe no they do to pay is a
Rug if you have the money you can actually get like
You wouldn't know about fucking to pay because you have no fucking hair. Oh my god. The first time I saw to pay free
That was in the Poconos
I was in high school my friend invited me with his parents to the Poconos
We went to some pool and his dad's hair fell off and like swam away. I was like what the fuck?
So first time I seen that
I think you're into like the 30s 40s and
Like everybody had like a hat on right so that was like a ball
Fuck so wait. We got to do two pays and dentures like what has got done to us put your hair down again
Stick your head down again. Let me see that shit. Oh, no, I got like the lighting here makes me look really bald, dude
Well, you look good, man. You guys a lot of
Right your forehead right there
too much I got it I got a lot of you know what the fuck the word up is
so he has a sunroof so what he's got a sunroof
Like it just it just went away, you know, so I don't know it's like it's really last
Although matters is the eyebrow shepherd like five years ago, dude
I mean what not completely I thought you know, it's still it's still kind of
What are you gonna do when your hair goes fully bald
Either you the shave it or it's gonna to paint I probably put like one of those like trucker trucker
You know, we're gonna use one of those little snapback fucking trucker or jump over
Yeah, but I don't like wearing hats, but
But like if I lose weight and shit, and I look and look you know when I lose weight
I get like a six pack and stuff like that. I might
I
Was a lot fatter than this, but I'm working on it. It's like let me see your physique. Come on
of the
the
Oh McQueen all right
So this Andrew, are you being a little bitch? I've been better than you you little bitch
You little criminal fuck kind of you just came out of jail now. You're Marty's Fox's house. How is that crippled bitch anyway?
And look, it says Alexander McQueen, Psyche, you're funny.
Haha, McQueen this McQueen is not in your mouth, bitch.
What month is this?
Shut up.
October.
It's not.
It's Ghosttober.
Get it right.
Bad boy.
Did I get out of jail just now?
Like, when did I get out again?
Get out of jail three months ago.
Take it.
You were in jail for a year.
I was on the phone with Marcy while she was calling you.
Dobs is in jail.
Ooh, ooh.
I remember before you went in, you were crying the weekend before you went in.
I was like, Dobs, you'll get through it.
Don't worry about it.
But look at you now.
Look at you now.
You were crying.
I don't got to go away because of my probation.
I told you to face it like a man.
You were on the run.
You face it like a man. All right. I was running smooth again. Good for you. Good for you, buddy
Who was I running from again from the law the law you want probation you fucked up?
All right, you had to turn yourself in and do a year, buddy
4 if I remember was a domestic violence charge we're not going to get into it
That's how Alexander mayors department shows you she'll have a panel tomorrow all about it like this guy named up
Wolves aka his real name. She's good
Alexander mayors is good my baby
Alexander be listening
There's your new target double of domestic violence talking about just came out of jail felon
He supports all the felons. I'm definitely not a felon
I mean, you know, mr. Miener you don't go to jail for a year for mr. Miener dick
You're definitely a felon. You said it many a time
You said it a million times. You're a felon my man. So now you're a liar felon as well
You're a liar felon
But I'm not interesting first no surprise there pal. Listen. You had me when you crashed through the wall in your underwear
With Kaz remember when they said do a handstand and you were so drunk and retarded and gullible that you were like, okay, guys
You let some little fat midget in the Bronx
Manipulate you to dive through a wall if nobody has seen it my babes
I saw Dub Wolves dive through a wall in his underwear
Because somebody told them to on a live panel
Yeah
You know that way he was so drunk like I'm double the loser and they're like yo
Dubs do a handstand and he tried to do a handstand and before he did it
He was like let me take my pants off because it like constricts my legs and they're like get take your pants off
So now he's in his boxers. What are now we have double in his boxers. This is two years ago
He does a handstand and goes through the wall his feet. He couldn't stop him
and he fucking broke the wall in his house
the next couple days he comes back he disappeared for a couple days because he knew we were laughing
and then he came back and he put like a blanket over the wall with tic-tacs or something to cover the
hole i remember that too but remember when you put a poster over the hole
mcqueef loves you dick mcqueer mcqueer
You who you do know you don't know what the fuck you're talking about you know that, right?
Everything I said is all fat and it's on stream and he won't back me off Marcy easy cats everybody
It was on live panel. You went to a wall in your underwear, bro cuz cats
Made fun of you and made you do it. You were his little puppet
That's funny because
Well, that's funny cuz oh, then I did a year in jail. That's funny. Oh
the
Yeah
It's all good
God I think fucking beautiful guy is like hey man go go ahead up there like I'm too scared tell them
Oh, he's cute. I was like I'll do that shit. Hey. Hey shepherd. You're pretty pretty beautiful. There's some shit
Wait, wait fire auto. I think I dobs you need to talk with Otto Otto's like he's a funny guy, dude
He's really super funny
I don't get up here, dude. I came up here to be funny
Nobody talking to no auto up here bullshit. I don't know what the fuck he's talking about
I don't know summer and the ladies. I don't hang out with the guys
You need anybody who wants the video I can send it to them. You're lying through your send it send it to them, please
she just
yeah, as soon as they
look at shepherd
I got them
look at your portals
hey, nobody fucking hide over your dumb ass
you fucking retard
how you doin
spider
so you saw Marcy live, does she have a nice eyes?
is it fat dogs?
is she a fat pig or is she like
looks human almost
is there anything that says human
and did you meet her um
four corners boyfriend
the indian dude
which is basically you with a wig
once again you don't know what the fuck you're talking about but go ahead
You literally make the content for itself. You fucking so retarded. You don't know anything you watch something
Years later and now you have such an opinion about shit, so I'm just wondering what those you ran away fucking fatty
Where'd he go? Where'd up a shepherd go my man shepherd?
look I only came up here to show where he was fucking cute because all right so
he's gone by day go at least I'm here with those retired me and go unless you
want to talk with me hey hey you know hey goes hmm go ahead and do your work for
this fucking piece of shit it's gonna be fun this be the head to your work all right
so you have no business here now right shepherds gone so you just hear a second
please come again
Your ghost wake the fuck up
It just ain't no in but holes and tricks like these nuts and suck this dick. I just heard that the other day
I find it funny.
please send the video dick it's exactly what i claim
they said yo yo fucking doves do a handstand and you're like oh marita okay
and then you try to do it and you fucking goon ass couldn't do it so you're like let me take
my pants off then you in your underwear and did it and you crashed through the wall send the video to
Goddy Goddy with his little voice. Oh what a dick
Uh, God, he can drop the link fire fire.
So even if I came here, God, he can drop the link.
Drop the link. God, he acts is going to be Alex.
No one wants to link.
Trust me.
You don't want to link my babes.
I want to take a chopo.
Take a five minute breath.
It's intermission.
Get your little panties, you know, it's your makeup and come back to the party
Hit the link my peeps
Dottie can only drop it. He can't let you up psyche is the ultimate God up here in the stand
What's up fuckers
Why aren't those hock it
Hello
All right, what you digs in your hand
I tried guys, they ain't talkin'
Holler, bye
I was in the bathroom, what the fuck? Jesus
Come back up, baby
You people look crazy like I tried when they talking
My phone's in the living room. I went to the bathroom
Force Jackets once again
ghost did you see your little sister someone was here man you didn't say shit
i'm in the bathroom powdering my nose you know checking my hand
the fuck see this way people are crazy you think i have my phone sharp to my ass and the funny thing
is this always happens as soon as i mute up and go do something in my life i hear the phone
I gotta run through my mansion
Trip over furniture to get to the phone like I'm here dicks. I'm here relaxed
Who's vacuuming? He's vacuuming? Who the hell is he, Summer?
Jesus.
You see?
Can't trust a middleman.
She's out there with some other nigga vacuuming shit.
There is no link anymore fire fire links a race you lost your your chance. It's a small window guys
You what do you think this 24-7 link?
Gotta catch it
okay
Like being in prison when they tend to water on or Matthews who can shower like once a week like you gotta catch that shit
The water's on like jump in wash your balls and get out what catch it
This isn't water flowing 24-7
TPP open panel for the peeps my man. I just got a notification for
Anybody that still deals with that crazy shit
Ghost over we gonna call ghost over
I ain't scared of no ghost
There he is my man that means psyche's still alive see he let Otto up
My man out
So I'll be back my man, so go get a beer in you and get ready cuz that bitch is coming back
I can sell
i like your face it looks a little mexican it looks a little you know what you remind me of
you know that prison in el Salvador sea card you remind me of every inmate in that bitch
but you're missing the tattoos bro all you need is the tattooed face and you are sea card king
look at this little sea cat mother fuck you're your criminal fuck how many
families you got I can read the families right off your fucking eyebrows
bro just kidding man did you fall in love with flirty diamond no but that's
You like that you're into that. I mean, whatever if you're into that you're into that
I'm not gonna judge you but I just wanted to let you know in case you're not into that
It's a guy it's a fat Mexican dude, bro
Some show she does I've seen it once actually
she flipped over she put her leg up in her kitchen and i saw the bulge she has a big bulge bro
why you want me to judge you want me to judge people no i don't want it i know
i can start with you if you want me to fucking judge people
yeah go ahead start with me please start with something start somewhere pal
you gotta start my man you want me to throw stones bro
Huh
Sticks and stones might break my bones, but words will never hurt me auto
I don't
I don't judge no human being bro, but you think you're gonna fucking you think you're gonna fucking say something to me, right?
Yeah
You look like every Mexican fuck you like Trump's a dream of deporting
Like if they show like who we deporting your pictures should pop up like Otto like you're the poster boy for deportation and criminals
I must be hard to live with that face, honestly
Why don't you fucking pick yourself? Why don't you go fucking take yourself into the mirror look yourself into the mirror?
Let's see
TOO COOL, LITTLE AUTO!
Look at him!
Why don't you stop that too slow, you fool!
Get it over with, boy!
Don't fucking tell me anything
No slap tattoos and get it over with you like being half ass
You're trying to look hard and criminal
But go all out and put the ms 13 tattoo right across your nose and so just go for it, bro
Don't be a pussy. You can't be gang member. Yes or gang member. No or so. So you have to choose
Actually, I am a criminal. I'm no shit dickhead. No shit. I've been saying it since we met
Nothing, I'm just saying your criminal nothing about it
Criminal suck. Oh, why are you a criminal? Why are you criminal? Why can't you follow the law? I don't you don't like the law
You don't like the law
What's up, bro? Look at you barking
You look like you're barking, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss,
I don't know what happens when we talk to each other.
Do you know what happens?
I've got five other people looking.
Five other people looking?
What do you mean looking?
You can never catch me.
You can never catch me, mother.
Oh, oh, you're a narco.
I got you.
You have protection.
You have rings around you of security.
No, no, I get it now.
So I got to get to five rings of security?
Ooh.
The whole five losers. There's no one watching over you dickhead. There's nobody watching over you asshole. Shut the fuck up
This guy said I got five people watching over me. Oh
What a dickhead. Let me see those nipples gay boy
You know, you don't look good tonight. You got a haircut. You got a haircut
You did your beard
You look good still how old you how old you 30 and I'm gonna give you 35, but I know you're like 45
But you look good for your age
Right, you're definitely in your 40s, but you can you can pull 30s off
Three three people five people or I like homes
See people for people orally
Every time I make a cell is over 500
500 pesos every time you make 500 pesos every sale
That's funny. What are you drinking?
Well, wait, wait, hold on. What deal was that? Was that a course like this? I saw a mountain on the can
What was that big boy?
One people. Where's the great rules? Where's the patron?
So now oh your mathematician you got five people three people two people one people
Gotcha, gotcha. What's that?
Look at you. Oh, thank God. So my ticket is dick. I know you love this guy. I
Saw you destroy him once
Yeah, he was barking like a dog. Yeah
I
Didn't you have a pretty fucking like the lotion on his chest yep
Where's your lotion tonight auto don't even fucking try don't even fucking try are you talking to?
Who are you talking to? Who are you talking to? Hey you little short fuck
I asked who you're talking to. I haven't even said anything to you. So why the fuck are you talking to me like that?
Do you want the nice summer or do you want the bitch that had you barking like a dog last time?
The dog
Well a little bitch look at him
So how's your day auto
Remember last time we were on panel. We had lots of fun. Didn't we oh my god, he's scared of you
Oh summer as soon as you came over look at him. He's trembling. He's quiet
You were you were ribbon on the left you took lotion on your chest and then you were barking like a dog
You can't prove shit. It was a fun night wasn't it Otto?
You wanted to send you are
You wanted to suck diamonds dick
Do you remember that Otto?
What you were gonna let you were gonna let diamond peg you
Yeah
Raise your volume a little I want to hear him, you know if he's gonna book but you're like really low. Yeah
That's better it was it was very low I could barely hear you
Okay. Well, you know what about about diamond about diamond. I think she's cute
Trust me, I'm very aware that you're attracted to diamond. Hey, that's not wrong with that. Long as everybody knows what's going on
That's the only thing I care about
Hey, but hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, I love diamond. I love diamond. I love her spirit. I love diamond
So what what about you put that lotion all over your body the other night last time you were up here?
Definitely
So what summer? I also I also sell
But I had a great time that many bark like a dog. I
Also sell worth of five hundred dollars of coke. What about it? I'm sure you did you were yacked out that night
No doubt about it. Okay. Okay, you think you're not fucking you think you know, okay tonight
You can't do shit to me, bro. You can't fucking be on you know, I don't want to go start there
I never said I was gonna do anything to you. I asked you are you getting hot tonight?
Where is this fucking loser anyway? You seen the states? What are we talking here?
It looks like a white line oh, he's like a Laker large he's drinking
Like what's the
Okay, we want some cocaine stoop. What's okay? Yeah, yeah, are you doing cocaine tonight?
Do you want some cook
I
Know you do I asked if you were doing cocaine tonight because that lets me know how much fun we can have with you
Well, well you're too far away by the by the way you wait too far
Haven't you worked like a dog there a couple nights last time you were on panel so
Pushups I'll give you a hundred dollars if you make them go naked and do the cream thing 500
I'm in London, Ontario, Canada.
Are you pissing in the pants?
How much cocaine do you think I have on me?
Those are all things I have made people do on panels by the way.
Yeah.
In the pants, push-ups, sit-ups, jumping jacks.
You name it.
Right now.
How much?
How much how much how much fucking cocaine do you think I have on me right now, right?
You know it's some time. Oh he teased us like Aronies hit us with a song, baby
Like
I'll tell you are you doing any cocaine tonight? That's the question. I'm happy. I'm happy
Big boy, big boy big boy you Spanish trying to talk Spanish type guy over there
Thanks, Alex. You may not read the panel
I'm talking to summer. I'm talking to summer summer talking to me. Okay, but you're not answering any of my questions
So if you're not gonna answer my questions, I'm gonna let my brother talk to you
Well, what's up? What what do you want? All right, let's go at it. I
Wait till he's a little bit more fucked up. It's too sober for me
What do you want me to keep talking to Otto?
Human q-tip he looks like a line of cocaine. He's all dressed in white Otto stand up for me pal
I gotta see the pants. You definitely have white pants on
You want cocaine? Yeah, I want you to do some cocaine. Yeah, I want to see if you have blue jeans, I know you got it
But if you have white pants on oh
My man is looking good with the green puppy. He's got the green khakis
All right, so I was sporting the Calvin Klein bun down short sleeve with the with the fresh with the fresh white Peter
He's wearing the nice green khakis with the black belt
Well, this guy does a model shoot. He just did a model shoot. He got up like what? You want to see the belt?
You're way too sober you need to get hot drink some you need to smile
Because he's home alone he should have a woman next to him. He's not the obvious man on us, right summer
This people think I'm a joke
Of course we do, Dick. You're on YouTube. You're a joke.
I mean, you bark like a dog on YouTube. Of course we will take your joke.
Yeah, you're a joke, Dick.
I had your rubbing lotion on your body last time.
Ole!
Oh my god, I just picked your summer with the flower in her mouth.
Just doing the tango.
He shows up in red, with a hose and a grin
A Canadian hero, not sure what he's in
Flirty diamond, all those flames
This is for you, Otto. This is for you.
Oh, that's right, he is from Canada.
Right.
That's right.
It's not like I'll take you out to the dock, huh?
Ha ha!
Blurredy diamond and auto!
I'm here.
What?
You want a bite of coke?
He's so free, he wants to get paid
I want some coke
So much
I'll give him some coke
Get that shirt out
The bag came
I'll give you some coke
Come to London. I love that song. That was beautiful.
Sex
He's a fucking immigrant dickhead
Isis probably on on rock your house right now my man
Look at that nose
the
You want to be a penguin, be a penguin.
A penguin?
Alright, I'll be back.
I gotta go finish my while spellings.
There you go.
Don't get locked out again for ten hours and please do that.
Remember that?
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck
Two lines, you do lines. I don't listen Jose one want you to
What is our Stanford?
Yeah, you fucking do some you fucking do lines you fucker. I do I you bet your ass
Why let me see. I don't believe it. They stop talking about jobs. It's like he's fine. Anyway, cuz that's bad
We can't show that up here. I do lines you do lines. All right, but we're not gonna show the lines. Okay
Who the fuck are you anyway? I'm in New York, man. New York City the capital
Uy ch** bro, I can...
NYPD, don't you see the name?
NYPD, that means New York Police Department.
What do you, what do you think I am?
Uy!
Uypa!
Parry!
¡A la guardiente, mío! ¡Sacá la guardiente!
¡Ah! ¡No es María Pueblón!
¿Aquí qué es la guardiente?
A blade in her hand, a fire in her eyes, oh bright
This is me, Ado, this is me, baby
I was telling you about the brand of coke
I've been a Canadian hero, I'm not sure what he's in
Ado, listen to your song, this is your 30-diamond song
Have some respect
You want that big burrito in your mouth?
You want the mexican guys copying your mouth?
Bloody diamonds for fam mexican dudaro!
Are you into that my man?
Hey, hey, come to love in my space
Come to love in my space
Out there with my friends
And we can have fun, have fun
Like out here, tonight I cook
Because I can toss up ghosts in a fucking flurry diamond outfit.
You and ghosts can go at it, right ghosts?
You can run it for real with auto. You can run it in that ad.
Shut out the fucker.
Ghost is running in an auto vest.
Shut up the diamond.
Let's run it, dawg.
Hey, what the fuck are you doing?
Why the fuck are you talking to me?
What the fuck are you doing here?
The burden of proof is on you dog!
Let's run it in your ass!
Ouch!
I don't know where you're going.
What the fuck are you doing here?
I don't care about your dog.
He's still barking like a chihuahua
I don't want it. I don't know it.
Let's talk to you.
No man, I don't appreciate these people fucking talking to me.
I don't even know them.
Don't talk to me, bro. I don't even know you bro. Don't talk to me bro. Don't talk to me man. I'm a Mexican
Where's Florida? I mean we need him
Florida come up and get your boyfriend, bro
Thank you you take you something
You think you tough
Bro, I hate my black pants. I hate black pebble. You think you're tough.
I can say this, I can say this in a matter of 10 seconds. Fire, fire. That's who I am.
Who the fuck are you?
Okay, okay, so if you've got money you can buy coke from me
No, I have my own coke dick. You can buy coke from me shit
How do you get stupid coke the fuck up a peace plan for Gaza a ceasefire in place
But Hamas is choosing terror and on a ramp
Let this soft mineral melt in your mouth to rebuild your gums and teeth and never need a dentist again. Did you know?
Look at the fam Mexican dude. That's our boys. That's how it's green girl
By the way, I don't fucking connect
His name is David. I think so say hello David David. So
That is a Mexican guy with a cock. I guess it looks
Yes, if you're some freak that likes looking like guys and think they're cute like that's crazy both
But there's girls out there. I don't there's women
But you know to Easter on I
Don't want 30 diamond bad that turns them on and there's nothing wrong with that honestly, you know, that's why
Everyone's different
We should not judge our authority diamonds like you honestly and
When I first met flirty, I thought it was a girl too. I swear to God. I'm like, that's a hard girl
Thank God for shepherd
Yeah, bro, right I mean after bottle vodka like you know who wouldn't go at that I mean
but you know what the thing is I don't like wieners that's a thing though you
know like we know who does with mustard and you know after bogey
with a beer
Thank you, but I was in love look at our space. He's mesmerized. I don't really like splurge
Yo, we gotta get flirting out of together because they're both looking for love and
You can see it in Arrow's eyes, it's a little...
I mean, does the birdie have kicks now?
What the fuck?
I see a bat.
It's a bat.
Bro, you'll have to try Arrow Offer.
Arrow, fuck birdie forever.
Like, you'll never get off.
You'll just die fuckinger.
Right?
I can see it in that board.
That's love. That's love.
She got the she got the little fupa too, you know, she got the fupa
Jackie you're hilarious
Oh
Why is this random emote?
He's my own fucking shit knows that I'm emo
That's funny as fuck to me. I went from such a
Oh my god, I gotta get out of this one. No, no, no
Like I really am I'm really going through a lot of shit no cap baroni
I
Just hope someone looks at me the way I don't look in that party right now. That's the way everyone wants to get looked at
Auto you're showing your condoms remember get those get that stuff ready. You're gonna you gotta use like three or four
Oh Shepherd
You know, well, I mean, she has like a big leader, like that's like, I don't want somebody to have like a big leader, you know what I mean?
Yeah, I'm not gonna do the things that...
Yeah, that's a fucking big leader, dude.
If I hear Wiener again, I'm going to sound 11 and get me a double Wiener.
Get out, David.
Mr. Hot Mexican dude.
Get with me and do your job.
Third is the name.
And bullet did the change.
Put a cover back to fucking 7-11 to get out Wiener.
Then don't care.
I think it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it's great, but it
You know, you might, you know, you might be able to do something, but not the ones that are like, you know.
Do you want to get, do you want to get some Pepsi? Do you want to get some Pepsi?
Who, me?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know, I'm already drinking like soda, yeah.
okay imagine flurry diamond has been playing us this whole time and it's
actually a girl but I can fucking I can fucking direct you to some coke
I'm not gonna go around me power. I don't need more coke. The last thing I need is coke
I got the red connects from Cali to Mexico shitted shut the fuck up. Let's play the flirty diamond shit
I run this show
You're just a sugar daddy
Yeah. I I like me. I like me.
Okay, if you ever want to transport keys from Caledon, New York, you're gonna want to dip them in skunk pee
That's compete the shit. They spray when they're scared. It's called like like oh something seen
It's a liquid the little it's yellow
So Colombians are this crazy that they have skunk farms and they scare them and they collect the shit in
Fucking pots and then they get a kilo and cover it in that shit that shit
The dog cannot detect you can have a car loaded with 80 keys
They can run the dog around it three times and it will not hit.
It's already been proven.
My boys, welcome to the new generation.
Skunk.
E. Not T.
The shit that they shoot out when they get scared.
You collect enough of that.
You rub the kilo in it.
You cover the whole kilo.
Look it up on the internet, by the way.
That shit, as soon as the dog comes out of the cop car, it's already blind.
It's already the nose is burning the dog doesn't want nothing to do with the cop car
It's gonna run around the car for 30 times blind like give me away from this thing. It will never hit
Okay
Skunk for my man
How did he work I
Already proved it. I had a girl get pulled over check this out. I had a girl get pulled over
From Cali in a rented car to New York. There was a kilo in each door panel four kilos
Covered in a stunk shit. They said were you coming from the back? We're gonna get the dog go ahead
They ran around twice didn't hit they gave her a ticket for like not changing lanes
Like not signaling what changing lanes still waiting back in New York with the four keys
Stunk juice my peeps
Well, I was pressed for you auto. I was pressed for you auto auto. I want you to leave flirty diamond
Hey, oh, hey, oh, hey, I don't need your
That's not safe. That's Pam when the way it is on his name is pain
You want some white sugar?
No.
auto I want you know I don't it's your
right it's gonna use you like a condom okay there you go what you want me I'm
gonna I'm gonna do you right okay oh it's gonna come in the condom pass it off
we use it it's gonna get me used it's gonna pass around mad talk about a fire
burning my house and use your hose
I don't use is like the regular he uses a regular size like those are like
He doesn't even know
Imaging right like an illegal alien criminal
Surgery doesn't even use Magnum auto. Do you know what a magnum Magnum is like? Yeah, that's what big black cock Magnum
That's dirty. That's ten inches in the auto. I don't need extra small
That's not a black dude
I'm not super large. I'm not super large. I'm like, I mean, I mean, I'm large, I'm not super large.
This is it. It's golden.
Sike. Yes.
Sike, you do. Do you like, do you like cocaine? Do you like coke?
Does a chicken have lips?
No, no, for real. For real. Do you like cocaine?
No, I'm just free and proud auto. What are you talking about? You're trying to get me to the gang life
And deal with any more gang members
Captain London Ontario come to London Ontario. I got me there to bring the way
Do you know how many miles away he is right now, he's in redondo beach you buy me a plane ticket at least
I mean, it's like that's a lot of work. It sounds like
psych I got I got a grand I got a grand for 80 80 80 give me 80 bucks you'll
get a gram of coke for real I shouldn't be doing drug deals all over my show so
let's yeah
You're supposed to be like, you know
Skunk juice if you look it up the things that comes out of the skunks ass when they're scared
It's it's a yellow liquid, right? If you look that up it has nothing to do with
Drug transporting but it will tell you on Wikipedia that dogs canines
It's their worst nightmare. It's kryptonite. So Colombian narcos caught on to that
They they can smell things a mile away a dog, right?
That shit
And just
but i got coke. nah bro you know what you do say you gotta get a dumb like 22 year old girl right
that doesn't have nothing to worry about you tell her listen i'm gonna send you to california
you're gonna go to enterprise you're gonna rent this car you tell her what car to rent check this
out three days before she goes to rent the car we rent it we take it to a house we strip the car
and says I need a rent a car and she picks that car out which is loaded and now she has to drive that
New York for 10 grand
I don't know I'm not talking about stripping enterprise rent a car, but please this is a nightmare. No
This is all just entertainment purposes only. This is a joke
He's not serious
He doesn't know anything about it. He wouldn't know he's never done that before he would never do that is
I still talk. Oh my god. He doesn't even notice it that he's not he's been off for like five minutes
He's still talking. I mean
Person with a louder mouth invented the world. I don't think so now somebody goes
I don't think there's a way. I don't think that I don't think there's a way that you motherfuckers will pinpoint me in London, Ontario
Okay, Paul, I don't know if I can take it anymore and I think they're
Saying some kind of drug deal. I don't I don't know what's going on
But I don't I don't feel like being in the middle of this right now. I mean
What are what are you up to?
You wouldn't be important me, but I got your cocaine
I don't I don't know why I've been banned in your chat for the I don't know I haven't checked today
But I think I've been banned for like a few days. I don't I don't know
The mods are upset the mods are upset, okay
Oh, well, I'm just gonna have I'm gonna have to end right now because all they want to talk about is, you know
transsexuals and and cocaine. Oh wait play music. Okay. Maybe you should just play music. Yeah. Yeah
Play your music
I'll play a song. Okay. Oh, yes. Yes. Yes. You hear a song? Okay. Let's see. Yes. How about
Oh, the cat, the little cat, what?
I'll be back, I'll be back, I'll be back.
Inside the machine, I'll wake up deeper
When I sleep, you'll understand when I delete
I went to God just to see, and the service showed me me
Heaven and hell were binary lies
When I ascend, your ego dies
Scar, can you feel my power?
Click here and your world gets smaller
Scar, scar, can you feel my power?
One spark and your truth gets darker
Cut your idols into data streams and pray to pixels for your dreams
My realms aren't affected, there's a door through the screen
I spoke it real and it became
There's a dream inside the machine, I wake up deeper
When I sleep, you'll understand when I bleed
I went to God just to see and I was logged in as me
Heaven and hell were empty drives, when I'm cold no flesh survives
Can you feel my power?
Click here and your world gets smaller
Score, score!
Can you feel my power?
One spark and your truth gets darker
Every vision I show you's a piece of my
Both our breathes cost me a price
was watching me heaven and hell were both my screens when i'm light the dark red
I push cocaine.
Okay, okay, okay, that's enough, that's enough.
No, no, no, no, no.
Stop talking about cocaine.
Okay, I'm gonna play another song.
You can say as long as you want.
I push cocaine.
Don't push cocaine.
You're talking about, I don't care about your cock.
Stop talking about it, okay?
Hold on one second.
I make money.
I make money pushing cocaine.
Hey, hey.
You use money.
Hush.
Okay, thank you very much.
Okay
Where's my money I'm making money. Oh, I heard you the first hundred times that's shush
I mean, please I mean goodness gracious. Keep some things. We're on the you're on the internet from everybody, please
In the city of mirrors and smoke
Where is my freaking song?
You wanna go cocaine?
Come to mommy
Let me get off the show auto
You wanna play with me?
What?
What site?
We're not talking to the boat, we're not talking to the weed.
The never-lack
Who does he think he is?
They tied better aim your curses right
One night, one more stream
Thanks for the chaos
Thanks for the dream she bent
With ghosts we help create
Got a keyboard army, but no paycheck yet.
Sending pizza, scrap man, manure at the door.
He just shrugs, nothing new there
Your hate is your hobby, your life's in a bind
He's livin' in color, you're stuck black and blind
Kowalski, the troll in the night
Tryin' so hard, but you can't win the fight
Da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da
without fear the devil binds what the fool released and both whispered
Sections that switch sides
Order chaos, welcome to the field
The fairway
Got it throwing shades, Iggy putting on a show
Rans laughing while JT's
Got receipts with circus clowns
And digital seats
Midnight chats and pixel fights
Trolls and armor, neon lights
Bandhammer swing, but I still say hi
Cause chaos is love
JT drops the diss track, ran lights and smoke
Gotti says something deep or maybe just a joke
JT's in the corner, dropping prophecy lines
Meanwhile, I'm the priest of this circus divine
Christine's mad about crystal Tony's just full of it
Braun's chicken struts around but it's looking like a lunatic
Sweet pea is gone sour beat high
Welcome to the Psyche Hater's Club
Where the gel is gathered up
Begging for attention, thirsty and stuck
One club I'm happy, I'm not part of
Go hate yourselves
Yeah, go hate yourselves
Bronze chicken pluck those feathers
Welcome to the...
LES is ready to come up here, but as soon as you enter the room he disappeared interesting. Are you LES perhaps?
Hello
Go he is
So LES is ready to come up here and then let him up man. He laughed soon as you came up
Why cuz I poem gum this is and told him a lesson made him a man
That's not him. I don't think that's him. Is he still live if he's live
It's definitely not him if he's not live it could be him. It's this person right here
Put the banner up, bro. Hey, I had it up and that's why he left maybe
There you go. I
Don't think it's him. He wouldn't come up. They've been talking a lot of shit about saccharones
It looks like him
Who would pretend to be him though?
Anybody that wants to put a cock in your face. I mean they pretend to be me
Let him talk with the banner up and identify him
Yes
Yo, yo, yo Alex, why you buy you a fucking bitch motherfucker. That's him. That's him. That's him. That's my man
Banner down banner down. No, it's him. It's him. Why you why you are you are your assholes? I'm fucking on Alex
I didn't do that. Hey, what you a fucking dick you pussy ass nigga. What do I do now, bro?
Keep on yo keep on fuck on my shit. I'm a fuck you up. What did I do now?
So fuck on me niggas. I fuck on my panel nigga. I'm a fuck you up, bro
No, stop it. You're lucky. You're lucky. I thought you know the righty-bow lesson tonight my man
That's lesson number two
No shit, so what are you gonna do buddy? What are you gonna do buddy? What are you gonna do buddy?
Shit my man lesson number three is coming up. Yes, that was lesson number two
Oh
Put the banner
Why are you making a little faggot?
They come in a team.
They can't handle business alone.
They come together a little.
No, you're soft.
Alex, you're soft.
How am I soft, dick?
How am I soft?
I know when you live, nigga, they gave me your book.
I don't know.
Fuck, so pull up, nigga.
Pull up.
Nah, nigga, you don't fuck out of here, bro.
You think that means something to me, dickhead?
I know when you live.
Shut up, dick.
You like that.
You like how I blocked your whole ship for an hour.
Block, block, block, block, block.
You can't stop me.
LES, LES, remember when you said this was the last time
you'll be up on my shit and I said no I won't?
Remember tonight my man?
I got you, you want to try.
Okay, good, good, learn, learn my boy.
You're gonna try bitch
You know at least Wanda Wanda loved it Wanda was laughing. Okay, you should be more like one
You're not welcome in my side
my side
I don't want to be welcome on your doxin shit
with you in easy
easy is giving you directions of how to go on your gps
and look at the backtracking
so you can doxy elise studio
you are trying to doxy elise studio
I don't want nothing to do with that, dick
like shut up man the fuck up you little doxy fuck you pussy nigga your mother's a pussy
no sorry sorry about that i will put your your girl's a pussy you little pussy bitch and you're a pussy
hey kid you're trying to doxy like studio why the fuck is that about bro can you just move on and
live your own life man
Why you don't want to tell it easy shit easy has an evil heart all he wants to do is dox people
Because this guy is such a loser his only little power in his life is doxing you understand
He feels powerful that way, because he has no power at all, but he thinks here, like I'll find you, I'll pull up my nigga, I got you, you know what I got, I'm about that life, it is what it is, they do what it is, my little hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello
you like that right you like that i just come in you can't stop me you don't want to run away
i blocked your whole shit i'll do it again dick next time you go up i'll do it again i still
have a wrench you're so stupid that it just oozes out of you bro you don't have a wrench
you know you don't have a wrench shut up you went through all of that oh xr1 by the way i'll psyche
I don't care, you're married to Bronzeberg's adopted sister hiding off-stage.
I have all your names, but I don't lower myself to your shit. I have exiles full docs,
I have LESs, I have EZs, easy by the way, let me doc some again.
2142 sort of
His real name is Alex Crespo, okay?
Easy cameras on his name is Alex Crespo
He lives at 2142 sort of in the Bronx
He's on the run for stabbing Eli the people. Yo, that's me bitch. Come it. That's me bitch
Alex nobody's worried to anybody that wants to know hi. My name is Charlie. That's the name behind the avatar
And then my name is
My real name is Lorenzo. Yeah, my real name is Lorenzo. Yeah
One more you want to say your name is Leslie
His name is Lorenzo. This real name is Leslie. That's what less fans for Leslie
You guys are all retarded old loser freaks that couldn't pull up to nothing, bro
The only person that have balls to pull up to people is now on the run
Easy was your only little puppet
Your little like the Rikers puppet
No one's pulling up, no where
No one's pulling up, no where bro
If you can't put in batteries and easy's back
No one's pulling up anywhere
So those days are over
Easy was your little genie pig that'll go stab people and throw his life away for you morons.
Like Eli almost did to him.
Eli told him to get a gun and come kill me.
Okay?
And you do the same shit to Easy.
You manipulate, you know, a little weak mind.
You use them like a little puppet and those days are over.
So who's gonna pull up?
Exile one? Exile one's not pulling up.
Let's say pulling up.
Nobody's pulling up.
Yo, yo, come to the top, come to the top, subscribe to us.
Shut up, come to the top.
Nah, nigga, nah, nigga, nah, nigga, fuck up, man.
You guys are done with this bullshit.
2025, I'll smack the shit out of both of you.
Hell, yes, I seen you.
Between you and Bruno, Eli, you look like a little cracker.
They're not lying with the cracker shit.
You need to eat my man. You need to get some meat on those bones. You actually look like a
120 pound little freak with a little cat. Your mouth is a lot of bark, bro. But you ain't doing shit, man.
Come on, bro. You're the fuck up. You're the last two of our worries.
Thompson, square, poke, nigga, you tell your girl, I know your girl loves me, I know your girl is next to you laughing
Cause she's like, tell Alex, your girl loves me more than you, bro
It's not funny, your wife likes Alex McQueen more than you're the man.
You can't even shake your dick up, motherfucker.
You belong in Australia.
You might make a stage hard all day every day, bro.
You understand?
I have the perfect remedy for that.
You don't give me 30 fucking words.
You don't give me that.
That's why I say it's hard.
How can you stick each other?
I don't give a fuck, man.
Knock it down.
Oh!
Ah!
Huh?
Yeah, stop being a little doxxing faggot. Don't be like Exxon easy, bro. Don't follow their lead. Those are losers
Yeah, I'm on the winner side
Yes, could you still have a chance, brother?
But it seems like you're following the losers, bro
You want to be a loser be a loser? You want to be a winner be a winner, bro? It's up to you my man. Honestly, you know
How are you a winner you took them but else you moved away from your house for three days when he's he pulled up
Yeah, okay says what
You're making of Disney stories I moved away from my house when he's he pulled up shut up
How you have lost your mind
You know you just go to make of a lies like oh
Wake up ways like nobody's gonna believe that dick
Oh! He moved away!
You should put down your move away!
喜歡叫Shut up!
You f**king loser!
You fucking loser, bro, get in your game.
Your game is weak and it's old, brother.
Get in your game.
Get in your game, my man.
No, you get on your knees.
You get on your knees.
Roll up.
You know the adi.
You know the adi, son.
Roll up.
I put a fucking bullet in your head right now.
Bull up.
I get it.
You moved.
I bet you moved.
I get it.
By the way, AC didn't pull up for nobody.
you understand nothing you have a video of some guy looking around a building
McQueen he never pulled up on a McQueen because guess what if he did he would not be alive right now
Eli would have never got stabbed if me and easy met i would have been in the ground right then and
And it's still an open case, he's such a faggot, oh someone called the Yankers PD and there's nothing, someone called the Bronx boat, there is an active warrant for this loser, you morons, there is an active warrant for Alex Crespo, 2142, his mom's name is Mercedes, EC's mom's name is Mercedes.
Why do you love so much, Alex?
On a midnight stream, neon eyes and conspiracy dreams
Talking cult in the desert sands
Tattoo maps and shaking hands
She's got screenshots, names and days
A tinfoil halo, ceiling fades in a chatroom chapel
Saints confess every broadcast feels like a holy mass
She might be right, dropping bombs in the middle of the night
White rose, black vans, symbol of sex
Oh Lord, what will she say next?
Crazy clothes, gang, some traffickers
Crystals live with the digital saboteurs
Truth or fiction, doesn't matter much
She's fire and static and psychic, too
I've seen the cymbals and the cornfield glow
Her angels whisper through the radio
There's always a villain and a secret cabal
And crystals, they're exposing it all
One moment sweet, next she's fierce
She's part oracle, part in a net myth, half the room's scared, the rest subsist
Her eyeliner is sharp as a truth dissected, and everything relieves the chat infected
You can laugh, but you're still tuned in, because she's chaos wrapped in porcelain skin
the streams on fire and the pixels blue
cold games, lies in shadow sex, here we go